<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[A17] Backup Generators</name>
  <author>DamnationLtd</author>
  <url>https://github.com/jakevose/rimworld_backup_generators</url>
  <targetVersion>0.17.0</targetVersion>
  <description>Backup generators provide a stopgap to prevent black/brownouts when battery reserves are depleted. They're fuel-expensive, so don't rely on them for consistent power!

&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;
* Generators start producing power when connected reserves are critically low (&lt;= 200 Wd) and stop when reserves exceed 1000 Wd or their power is flicked off/on
* Wood and Chemfuel versions are provided; the chemfuel version unlocks upon researching Refining

&lt;size=24&gt;Specifics&lt;/size&gt;
* Each generator type should appear in the Power category when the research requirements are fulfilled (see: Change Log)
* Backup generators only work on power grids with connected batteries
* Backup generators consume several times more fuel than Vanilla fueled generators when active; they're really only meant for emergencies
* Generators consume some fuel even when idling, although less than power-producing Vanilla fueled generators
* Chemfuel backup generators are twice as efficient as their wood-fueled counterparts, both when idle and providing power

&lt;size=24&gt;Feedback Welcome&lt;/size&gt;
Let me know if there are bugs, balance issues, or features you'd like to see!

&lt;size=24&gt;Change Log&lt;/size&gt;
2017/04/06, 1.0: Initial release
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
2017/04/07, 1.1: Balance tweaks
* Wood backup generators now last ~1 season/load idle and ~1 day/load running
* Chemfuel backup generators now last ~1 year/load idle and ~4 days/load running
* Both generators now require MultiAnalyzer research instead of just Electricity
* Chemfuel still requires Refining research

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
2017/04/08, 1.2.1: Behavior additions
* Generators can now be minified, i.e. installed/uninstalled
* Since they generate some amount of heat, the heater hinting shows when placing generators
* Documentation flub on 1.2

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
2017/07/14, 1.2.2: A17 support
* Thanks to ProximityMicrowave for beating me to the punch!

&lt;size=24&gt;Roadmap&lt;/size&gt;
* ~Balance tweaks~
* ~Install/uninstall capability~
* Advanced 1x1 versions (more research and a few rarer resources; probably a bit more efficient still)
* On/off thresholds configurability
* Other options?

&lt;size=24&gt;License&lt;/size&gt;
Please feel free to pull this apart and make any derivative work you like as long as it's not a straight copy to claim this work as your own. Attribution is not required but is always appreciated.
  </description>
</ModMetaData>
